Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Visual Images, 1889-2019 UPG.RG.60
ULS Greensburg
- Prints (PR), 1969-2014; V.
  - Dance Team [UPG Bobcat Dancers], 1998-2008 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 6, Box 3)
    2002/03. Group photo. Individual photos.
    2003/04. Group photo. Individual photos.
    2004/05.
    2005/06.
    2006/07.
    2007/08.
    2008/09. [UPG Archives does not hold a print. faz 1/14/10]
    2009/10. See Cheer/Dance Team
  - Da Vinci Society [Da Vinci Scholars], 2002 (Map-case 1)
    See: UPG.fRG.60 Prints--da Vinci Society--1st Induction Ceremony [Housed in Map Case]. For photographic print of first inductees, See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Ser.: Prints, Cultura, La. 2002.
    - Da Vinci Scholars Induction Ceremony, December 7, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 3)
      2007 Da Vinci Scholars: Amy Duli, Troy Eans, Nicole Garcher, Justin Karapandi, Megan Redfoot. Archives has two sets of prints plus 2 CD-Rs.
  - Day of Caring, September 13, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  - Debate Team, 1983 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 1)
  - Endowments (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  - Engineering Society, Engineering Club, 1969 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 3)
    For 1969 photo See: UPG.qRG.60 Prints.
  - Faculty & Staff vs. Students Charity Basketball Game, 2011-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 6, Box 3)
    3/24/11 (3rd Annual)
    4/2/12 (4th Annual)
  - Faculty Awards, 1995-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 1)
    1995 1996 1997 1998
  - Faculty Staff Awards, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 3)
    from left: Barbara Barnhart, Lab. Instr., Distinguished Svc.; Dr. Martha Koehler, Asst. Prof. of English, Distinguished Teaching; Joseph Olczak, Dir. of Plant Maintenance, Pres. Award for Staff Excellence; Dr. William Rued, Assoc. Prof. of Philosophy, and Elizabeth Tiedemann, Dir. of Career Svcs., Pres. Citation for Distinguished Svc.
  - Fall Festival, 1983-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 6, Box 3)
    1983 Videocassette format: See: UPG.RG.60 VCIII.A.1
    1984
    1985 No prints Filmstrip (Negative): See: Oversize print file folder
    1986 Prints. See also: 1 print Oversize print file folder Videocassette format: See: UPG.RG.60 III.A.2 DVD format: See: UPG.RG.60 DVD24.B.2 (Track 2) Slide format: See: UPG.RG.60 SB3 (Slider Binder 3)
    1988
    1991 No prints Video cassette format: See UPG.RG.60 VCIII.A.2
    1996
  - Flagpole [Athletics Field], September 1, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 3)
    Dedication
  - Fountain, 2000-2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 6, Box 4)
    Construction. Ground base line. Water and electric lines. Construction. July 11-Oct., 2000. Fall, 2000. Apr.?, 2001. Fall, 2001.
  - Freshman Convocation [First-Year Student Convocation], 1997-2005 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 6, Box 4)
    1997 [1st]
    1999
    2000
    2002
    2005 [First-Year Student convocation]
  - Freshman Move In, 1998, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  - Friends of the Millstein Library Scholarship, April 16, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 1)
    Scholarship Reception. Nicole Costella, 1st winner of the scholarship.
  - Golf Team, 1996-2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 7)
    1998/99 AMCC Men's Golf Champions. Luncheon.
    2000/01 Group photo. Individual photos.
  - Greensburg Bicentennial, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 1)
    1799-1999
  - Hempfield Area High School Marching Band, 2005 (Map-case 1)
    116th Tournament of Roses Parade, Pasadena. (10"x18") [Filed in Map Case: UPG.fRG.60 Ser.: Prints]
  - Homecoming, 1999-2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 1)
    1999. King. Queen. Reception. Homecoming King, Sal Molitierno; Homecoming Queen, Brandy Valentine.
    1999. King and Queen candidate
    1999. Pep rally.
    1999. Sports activities.
    1999. Greensburg Bicentennial, 1799-1999.
    2000. Arts of Mexico Demonstration and Exhibit. Felipe Hernandez Vicente, master weaver. Maria de los Angeles Guerraro Diaz, painter of Oaxacan animal wood carvings.
    2000. Presentation of "Oaxaxa En UPG", a weaving by Felipe Hernandez Vicente to Dr. Frank A. Cassell on the occasion of UPG Homecoming 2000.
    2000. Activities.
    2001. Homecoming King, James Woodson. Homecoming Queen, Andrea Doner.
  - Honors Convocation, 1999-2008 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 1)
    1999 [1st]
  - Humanities Day, 1985-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    1985
    1986
    1993
    (For video cassettes: 1983, 1994, 1991, 1992, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998. See UPG.RG.60 VCIII.B1-12.)
    (For DVD format 1983, 1996, 1997, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD 24.B.3 1983 (Track 1, 2); 1996 (Track 3); 1997 (Track 4)
  - Ice Hockey Club [Pitt-Greensburg Ice Hockey Team], 2013-2014 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    [copy of photo downloaded from UPG website: www.greensburg.pitt.edu/news]
  - Indian Classical Music Concert, March 29, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
  - Joan Chambers Children's Collection, 1995 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    Dedication. Reception.
  - Kuntu Repertory Theater, October 10, 1986 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    Performance of To Be Young, Gifted, and Black: A Portrait of Lorraine Hansberry in Her Own Words, at UPG.
  - Lambda Pi Eta [Communication Honor Society], March 21, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
  - Leadership Recognition Awards Banquet [later Leadership Recognition Awards Ceremony], 1998-2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
  - Leadership Recognition Awards Ceremony, 2002-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 7)
    See also: Oversize Prints
    For programs, See: UPG.RG.52 Ser: Leadership Recognition Awards Ceremony
    2009
    2010
    2011
    2012
  - Lieberman, Sen. Joseph, November 3, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    Vice Presidential Candidate, Democratic Party, Election 2002, Campaign Stop.
  - Lynch, Charles McKenna, 1884-1963 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2, Map-case 1)
    Framed painting, color. painting: 49cm x 35.5cm: with frame: 70cm x 60cm [Housed in Map Case: UPG.qRG.60]
    CD containing black and white photograph of CML.
  - Lynch Estate, 1963 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2, Map-case 1)
    View of what is the present site of Smith Hall parking lot. ca. 1963. Framed folio photograph.
    Lynch Hall. 3 framed folio photographs. Includes side views. ca. 1963.
    Lynch Hall. view of what became the road to Powers Hall and Lynch Hall from Mt. Pleasant Road, ca. 1963. [Housed in Map Case: UPG.RG.60]
  - Lynch Family, June 3, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    Gift of Lynch Family items [armchair, footstool, framed embroidered picture of George Washington].
    [For provenance, see UPG.RG.02.4 Pres. Cassell, Dr. Frank A. Ser.: Correspondence.]
  - Lynch Family Album, September 2, 2002 (Map-case 1)
    Lynch Family Album. [v. 2, Houses in the Families and Other Points of Interest. 33 sheets 12" X 18" Color photocopy of an album of 140 photographs of the houses, residences, and estates of various members of the Lynch Family taken by Libby Schmidt, grandaughter of Commander Lynch and daughter of Judge Rial. Also includes photographs of other points of interest, i.e., Westmoreland Museum of Art, Blessed Sacrament Cathedral, the old [Greensburg] Library, the old [Greensburg] post office (now the Greensburg Library), Greensburg Central Catholic High School, First Presbyterian Church of Greensburg, First United Methodist Church, Christ Episcopal Church, Westmoreland County Courthouse, Royers Department Store, Troutman's Department Store, Barclay's Westmoreland Trust Co., First National Bank (now Southwest Bank), Coskey-Nicholson Funeral Home, Lynch Mausoleum, Keppel Funeral Home, St. Clair Cemetery (off Route 30), Westmoreland Polo & Hunt Club, Arthur St. Clair Park, Elks Club, YMCA, Greensburg Train Station, Penn Albert Hotel, Yancey's, Lynch Field, Roadman's Lake (State Run Road), Seton Hill College. This color photocopy made by Business Partners, Jeanette. Sent to the UPG Archives by the Office of the UPG President, Sept. 2, 2002. [Housed in Map Case. See: UPG.qRG.60 Prints. Lynch Family Album]
  - Mascot [UPG Mascot] [UPG 6th Man], 2002-2009 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 7)
    Image: 2002, Nov. 1
    Picture of Mascot on postal card. [Fall, 2009]
  - Mathis, Judge Greg, February 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    "Television Courtroom Judge at UPG," Black History Month.
    For videocassette See: UPG.RG.60 VC VIII.10.
  - NCAA Div. III Conference, September 4, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    Conference Membership Acceptance Picnic
  - Natural Sciences Capstone Laboratories [basement of Smith Hall], 2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    Base Line 6/8/01 Construction. July-Aug., 2001.
  - Nieto, Reuben Alfonso Lopez, April 2, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    Reception
  - Nine/Eleven [9/11], September 11, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 2)
    1st Anniversary Commemorative Service of the terrorist attack on the World Trade Center.
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: World Trade Center, Terrorist Attack On, 9/11/01.
  - Palekar, Priya. Soprano, April 10, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
    Recital at UPG.
    See: UPG.RG.61 C.9 for audio cassette.
  - Parking Lot [East of Greensburg/Mt. Pleasant Road. University Court Parking Lot], August-October 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
  - Parking Lot [Academic Villages], July, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
  - Parking Lot [New addition, Lynch Hall], July 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
  - Patio [Millstein Library], 2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 2)
    Ribbon Cutting Ceremony 9/30/10
    Patio Furntiture. July 2010. [See: Oversize Prints]
    For construction of Patio, See: UPG.RG.60 Prints. Construction Projects 2010. Millstein Library.
  - Pavilion (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
  - Pedestrian Bridge, July 1987 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
    Construction View to Powers Hall View to Chambers Hall
    See also: Construction Projects 2010
  - Phi Eta Sigma [National Freshman Honor Society] UPG Chapter, April 15, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
    Installation and Induction Ceremony
  - Phi Kappa Phi [National Senior Honor Society] UPG Chapter, March 16, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
    Installation
  - Phonothon, February 21, 1984 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
    1st UPG Phonothon conducted from the Oakland Campus
  - Physics Workshop for Teachers, March 8-9, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
  - Pittfest, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
    Selection of King and Queen
  - Portraits
    n.b.: These portraits represent current and non-current UPG Presidents, Advisory Board Members, Faculty, and Staff as well as University of Pittsburgh Chancellors. This is not an all inclusive file but contains only those prints received in the UPG Archives. Please consult the "regular" and "oversize" print files.
    For available biographical information, see UPG.RG.51 Biographical Files. [faz 12/10/02]
    - UPG Presidents, 1962-2005 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 7, Box 3)
      Smith, Dr. Albert A., President, 1962-1980 See also: Oversize Prints.
      Chambers, Dr. George Ferguson, President, 1980-1996 See also: Oversize Prints.
      Chambers, Dr. George Ferguson, Retirement Party, 21 Nov. 1996
      Chambers, Dr. George Ferguson. With Architectural Rendering of Faculty Office Building. 1987.
      Chambers, Dr. George Ferguson. President's Reception for Faculty. Mid 1980's.
      Chambers, Dr. George Ferguson. Local Presidents Meeting. [undtd]
      Cassell, Dr. Frank A., President, Aug., 1997-2007
      Cassell, Dr. Frank A. Installation as President, March 25, 1998
      Cassell, Dr. Frank A. With Mrs. Tim Lynch. July 1998.
      Cassell, Dr. Frank A. Westmoreland Chamber of Commerce 2003 Annual Business Meeting.
      Cassell, Dr. Frank A. FAC receiving sports award presented by Richard "Dick" Hack, Director of Athletics and Recreational Activities. 18 May 2007.
      Cassell, Dr. Frank A. Group photo: Joyce Rossman, Beth Cassell, Frank Cassell, Daniel Gunderson, Jason Gongaware, Ewa Rudnicka, Christopher Marquette. Dec., 2003. [See: Oversize Prints]
      Cassell, Dr. Frank A. Group photo. Local College Presidents Meeting. [late 1990's, early 2000's]. Dr. Frank A. Cassell, Dr. Joanne Boyle, Rep. Allen Kukovich, Dr. Daniel Krezenski, Fr. Martin Bartel.
      Cassell Portrait [Dr. Frank A. and Beth Cassell] [portrait by C.W. Gibbons, 2005] See UPG.RG.60 FD2
    - UPG Advisory Board (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3)
      Billey, Dr. Peter
      Ciarimboli, Dominic
      Hoffstot III, H. Phipps
      Jones, Sr., William McMichael
      Peterson, Colleen
      O'Toole, Judith H.
      Singley, Luther
    - UPG Faculty, 1991-2006 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Box 4, Map-case 1)
      Barnhart, Barbara
      Barnot, Dr. Vickilyn "Vickie"
      Barsic, Nick
      Batenberg, Dr. Abram
      Beeson, Dr. Lillian
      Beeson, Dr. Lillian. Reception honoring her contribution to the UPG Village System. 18 April 2001.
      Bhatnagar, Dr. Rakesh K. [See also: UPG.qrg.60 Prints--Portraits--UPG Faculty]
      Blevins, Dr. Richard L.
      Boldurian, Dr. Anthony.
      Chew, Dr. Paul
      Cornell, Evan
      Covarrubias, Dr. Alicia V.
      Cruz, Dr. Felicia J.
      DeFloria, James
      Deininger, Jacob
      Denny, William J.
      Dugan, Dr. Mary Jane
      Ent, Dr. Veronica I.
      Estrada, Dr. Nancy B. SEE: Florez-Estrada, Dr. Nancy B.
      Evans-Rhodes, Dr. Debra
      Florez-Estrada, Dr. Nancy B.
      Gates, Patricia
      Greenfield, Dr. Sayre Nelson
      Guo, David
      Hahn, Susan
      Hart, Gary D.
      Hirsch, Dr. Steven J.
      Holzworth, Dr. Kerry W.
      Jensen, Marilyn
      Jew, Dr. Kimberly D.
      Kadunce, Dr. William
      Kadunce, Dr. WIlliam. Retirement Luncheon, 17 Apr. 2001 See also: Oversize Prints.
      Katzman, Dr. Stanley See also: Oversize Prints
      Koehler, Dr. Martha J.
      Koeske, Dr. Randi
      Koshinsky, Linda
      Kromer, Mrs. Jean
      Kuschmierz, Dr. Ruth See also: Oversize Prints.
      LaFollette, Tavia
      Levin, Dr. Colette G.
      Liddick, Donald
      Lindberg, Dr. William E.
      Lokay, Dr. Joseph
      Lucci, Michael J.
      Marciniak, Anne
      Marquette, Dr. Christopher
      Marsh, Dr. David
      Marsh, Dr. Diane T. See also: Oversize Prints.
      McColloch, Dr. Mark David
      McGlynn, Dr. Frank
      McWhinney, Dr. Norman See: UPG.RG.57 Principals. McWhinney, Norman N.
      Menz, Terri
      Milberg, Dr. Daniel
      Murabito, Dr. Stephen J.
      Nichols, David
      Nicoletti, Dr. Guy See also: Oversize Prints
      O'Donnell, Dr. Mary Grace
      Pamerleau, II, Dr. William Charles
      Poke, Dr. Carl F. Retirement reception as Dean. 2/27/91
      Poke, Dr. Carl F. [24" x 28" color photo of CFP in Map Case, UPG.q/fRG.60 Prints]
      Pratt, Robert J.A.
      Reilly, Dr. Donald T.
      Reilly, Dr. Donald T. Retirement Reception. 11/24/03. See also: Oversize prints.
      Roadman, Harriette M.
      Rossetti, Dr. Guy
      Rouse, Jeffrey P.
      Rudnicka, Ewa A.
      Rubinoff, Michael
      Sabadasz, Joel
      Scanlon, Dr. Norman W.
      Scanlon, Dr. Norman W. Reception given by Dr. Frank Cassell, 1997.
      Schmidt, Patricia A. Retirement Dinner. 27 April 2000, Portrait.
      Senor, Dr. Larry E. Retirement Party. 8 Apr. 2003, Portrait.
      Siegert, Dr. Jennifer L.
      Siegert, Dr. Jennifer L. Farewell Luncheon. 4 June 2002.
      Spore, Dr. Mary Beth
      Spore, Dr. Mary Beth. Farewell Reception. June 29, 2006. Includes a CD-R
      Sposato, Dr. Jeffrey S.
      Stangl, Patty
      Tamkewicz, Julia (Librarian) See: Oversize prints.
      Taylor, Roger
      Tietz, Julie
      Truxal-Hamburg, Dr. Merilyn
      Turkovich, Dawn M.
      Vana, Clara
      Viano, Joanne
      Vollmer, Judith
      Vyas, Dr. Manharal
      Waxwood, Dr. Vincenne A. Retirement luncheon. June 15, 2001
      Whatule, Dr. Larry
      Wilson, Dr. Franklin David
      Zaar, Karla
      Zaleskiewicz, Dr. Thad P. See also: Oversize prints.
      Zimmerman, Dr. Judith
    - UPG Faculty. Groups (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 4)
      Various
    - UPG Staff, 1997-2007 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 7, Box 4)
      Allemeier, Susan
      Altman, Michael (Mike) P.
      Andrea, Christina
      Antoniak, Karen M. President's Award for Staff Excellence. 10/30/98
      Antoniak, Karen M. Portrait, 10/7/07
      Azzarello, Kristine
      Bach, Julie
      Barris, Julie
      Belville, Mike
      Bergstrom, Jody Ann
      Berry, Bernard. Retirement reception, 7/29/04, Portrait.
      Bombach, Rich
      Bowers, Betty K.
      Brooks, Sharon
      Brusoski, Gail
      Bucchi, Joyce
      Calloway, Carol A.
      Calloway, Carol A. Staff Award 1997. See also: Oversize.
      Calloway, Carol A. Retirement Party 6/25/08. See UPG.RG.40 UPG Staff Association. Ser.: Activities Committee. Activities, Projects. Calloway, Carol A.
      Carter, Parris. See also: UPG.RG.60 Prints Staff Awards Luncheon 12/19/2003 President's Award for Staff Excellence
      Cerutti, Charlene Touvelle
      Chapman, Jerry
      Confer, Sheila
      Conlon, Kevin
      Connors, Helen
      Connors, Helen. Retirement Reception, 18 Apr. 2002.
      Cuneo, Donna Hart Henry
      Curiale, Mary
      Darr, Brandi
      Debnar, Lequeta
      DePaolis, Cheryl
      Dominick, Suzanne
      Douthett, Tracy
      Enlow, Gerry K.
      Evans, Nancy
      Exler, Erica
      Falkosky, Wendy
      Fetter, Jennifer
      Fleming, Crystale
      Furjanic, Matt
      Gavula, Karen
      Gazze, Ron
      Greenawalt, Mark
      Hack, Richard (Dick)
      Hammond, Sara
      Hayburn, Emily
      Henry, Donna Hart See: Cuneo, Donna Hart Henry
      Hill, Mary Louise
      Horan, Tom
      Jeffries, Laura
      Johnson, Michael
      Kahn, Marcus
      Kantorick, Mrs. See: Buildings. Lynch Hall. First Snack Bar.
      King, Linda
      Kelly, J. Thomas "Tom" Retirement Reception. 9/3/03, Portrait.
      Kettering, Valeria E. Portrait; Retirement Party, 6/25/03.
      Kikler, John [UPG Gardener; Caretaker later chauffeur Lynch Family] See also: UPG.RG.61 Audio Cassette C.17 for "Interview with John and Anne Kickler [Kikler]. July 22, 19??.
      Katarski, Mark
      Kolar, Debbie
      Kristan, Chuck
      Kubister, Nathan
      Kurtz, Julia
      Larko, Sue
      Laskey, Kevin
      Liebdzinski, Michael
      Lucovitz, Chris
      Mays, Karen
      McClain, Sr., Simeon C.
      McGrew, Bill
      Milburn, Carol Saunders
      Mileca, Shirley
      Miller, Martin
      Miller, Thomas B.
      Milne, Glenn
      Molinari, Donna L.
      Mudry, Dan
      Mugnano, Carole
      Munchinski, Dana LeViere
      Naccarrato, Richard
      Nauman, Michele Victoria
      Paul, Cynthia
      Peagler, Anne
      Poole, Beverly See: UPG.RG.60--Prints--Smart Growth Partnership of Westmoreland County
      Prinkey, James C.
      Ressler, Eric
      Ricco, Karen
      Robinson, Charles
      Rossi, Steven
      Royse, Carolyn V. See: UPG.RG.60 Ser: Prints--Smart Growth Partnership of Westmoreland County
      Schmidt, Cathy Retirement Reception 4/5/04, Portrait.
      Schmidt, Dr. David C. Retirement Reception 6/1/04
      Schober, Bonnie
      Seftas, Marie
      Sherbine, Kenneth
      Sherman, Amber
      Shuglie, Robin
      Sims, Kendra C.
      Sparks, J. Richard "Rick"
      Sparks, J. Richard "Rick" Farewell Luncheon, 24 May 2002
      Squires, Brad
      Statler, Scott
      Stern, Jared
      Stevens, Jaison
      Stouffer, Larry
      Sturm, Constance
      Swalga, Daniel (Dan)
      Swenson, Brad
      Swope, Denver
      Tracey, Michelle
      Turack, John
      Ungvarsky, Michael
      Valentine, Bryan
      Valentine, Jana
      Vertachnik, Janine
      Vinkler, Margaret (Margie) B.
      Warman, Lorna
      Weir, Dorothy J.
      Westbrooks, Charles I.
      Wilson, Harold
      Wilson, Kelly
      Yancey, Betsy
      Yeckley, James B.
      Young, Nancy [Also see: Gavula, Karen]
      Yurko, Carlene
    - UPG Staff Groups, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 4)
      Dept. of Safety and Security 7/25/06
      Millstein Library. Staff photo taken in Oct. 2006 upon the departure of Nancy Young. Includes: Patricia Duck (Director of the Library), Frank A. Zabrosky (UPG Archives Volunteer), Karen Gavula (former Millstein Library staff member), Clara Vana (Asst. Dir. of the Library), Jim Vikartosky (Library Specialist), Sandy Buehner (Office Services Specialist), Jacob Deininger (Public Services Librarian), Bonnie Chambers (Library Specialist).
    - UPG Peer Group Advisors [Peer Group Advisors; UPG Peer Leaders], June 29, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 4)
      Dohli, Keith
      Keller, Nicole
      Leljedal, Lauren
      Minnich, Jayson
      Qualk, Lindsey
      Rubin, Eric
      Saxinger, Brittney
      Sinay, Samatha
      Slafka, Aaron
      Small, Danielle
      Stonebraker, Jarid
      Whipkey, Robert (Trey)
    - UPO Chancellors [University of Pittsburgh, Oakland. Chancellors], 1956-1996 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 7, Box 4, Shelf 11, Box 2)
      Litchfield, Dr. Edward H. Chancellor, 1956-1965
      Posvar, Dr. Wesley W. Chancellor, 1967-1991
      Nordenberg, Dr. Mark A. Interim Chancellor, 1995. Chancellor, 1996-
  - Postcards (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
    Millstein Library with Campus Clock. 1 card with 5 scenes: fountain; Lynch Hall; Gazebo, Academic Village, UPG logo on entrance wall.
  - Quilt, 2002-2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 8, Box 1)
    "UPG Beginnings" Quilting Members. 2/28/02
    "Building UPG" [includes Quilting Members] 8/6/03.
  - Read for Lifetime Learning Program, 1998-1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
    Pilot Year
  - Real World/Road Rules, March 25, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
    Ace and Rachel
  - Registrar, 1985? (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
  - Renaissance Festival, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
  - Resident Assistants, August 20, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1, Shelf 11, Box 2)
    Group Photo; Group Photos by Resident Hall Resident Assistants 2007-2008
    See also: Flash Drive (FD 1) RA Training Fall 09
  - Ridilla Field (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
  - S.O.A.R. [Summer Orientation Academic Program], 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
  - Second Mrs. Demyan, The, September 1999 (Microfilm-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
    Original play by K.C. Constantine. Performance Cast
  - Segura, Prof. Juan, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
    1st Fullbright Scholar to teach at UPG. Reception. 1/25/00. Farewell Reception. 4/19/00.
  - Senior Recognition Day [Senior Recognition Ceremony], May 9, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
  - Senior Plaza, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
  - Sidewalks (Replacement), 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
  - Snowflake Ball, 1997, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1, Shelf 11, Box 2)
  - Soccer (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1)
    Soccer Field
  - Soccer (Men's), 1998-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 1, Shelf 11, Box 2)
    Scope and Content
    1999/00
    2007/08 Roster 2007
    2011/2012
  - Soccer (Women's), 2000-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 8)
    2005/06 (Roster 2005)
    2006/07 (Roster 2006)
    2007/08 (Roster 2007)
  - Softball (Women's), 1999-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 8, Box 2, Shelf 11)
    2008/09 No photos for this academic year in UPG Archives [faz]
  - Sports Awards Banquet [Later Sports Awards Reception/Ceremony], 1998-2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 2, Shelf 8, Box 3)